Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2017 RL.00924
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2011; 2399 Volumes
  - Islandian Campaign, 77
    - Plague of Terror (Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1583)
    - Streets of Gems (Bath, ME: The Companions, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1578)
  - James Bond 007, 78
    - Q Manual: The Illustrated Guide to the World's Finest Armory (New York, NY: Victory Games, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 593)
    - Thrilling Locations (New York, NY: Victory Games, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 594)
  - Jovian Chronicles, 79
    - Advanced Rules and Background (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1997 (Volume 2197)
    - Chaos Principle: Original Cinematic Adventure (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1998 (Volume 2195)
    - Cinematic Fleet Combat System: Lightning Strike (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1999 (Volume 2193)
    - Cinematic Fleet Combat System: Lightning Strike Companion (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2001 (Volume 2181)
    - Cinematic Fleet Combat System: Lightning Strike, Second Edition (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2000 (Volume 2186)
    - Cislunar Space: Planet Sourcebook (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2003 (Volume 2178)
    - Earth: Planet Sourcebook (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2000 (Volume 2187)
    - Europa Incident (Montreal, Canada: Ianus Publications), 1994 (Volume 2204)
    - Game Aid for Jovian Chronicles (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1998 (Volume 2194)
    - Jovian Chronicles (Montreal, Canada: Ianus Publications), 1993 (Volume 2203)
    - Jovian Chronicles RPG Player's Handbook, Second Edition (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2003 (Volume 2176)
    - Jupiter: Planet Sourcebook (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2000 (Volume 2188)
    - Lightning Strike Supplement One: Venus: Behind the Veil (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1999 (Volume 2192)
    - Lightning Strike Supplement Two: Call to Arms (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2000 (Volume 2191)
    - Mars: Planet Sourcebook (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2002 (Volume 2179)
    - Mechanical Catalog Two: Civilian Equipment and Spacecraft (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2000 (Volume 2190)
    - Mechanical Catalog: Exo-Armors and Spacecraft (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1997 (Volume 2196)
    - Nomads: Planet Sourcebook (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2001 (Volume 2182)
    - Roleplaying Core Rules: Silhouette Core, Version 003 (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2003 (Volume 2177)
    - Rules and Background for Jovian Chronicles: Enter the Saga of Mankind (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1997 (Volume 2198)
    - Shadow of Cega: Planet Sourcebook (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2001 (Volume 2184)
    - Ships of the Fleet, Volume Four: Venus Fleet (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2000 (Volume 2199)
    - Ships of the Fleet, Volume One: Jovian Confederation (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1998 (Volume 2202)
    - Ships of the Fleet, Volume Three: Cega Navy (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1999 (Volume 2200)
    - Ships of the Fleet, Volume Two: Jovian Confederation (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1999 (Volume 2201)
    - Solapol Sourcebook (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 1999 (Volume 2189)
    - Space Equipment Handbook: Advanced Tools & Weapons (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2000 (Volume 2185)
    - Spacer's Guide: A Guide to Life in the Twenty-Third Century (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2001 (Volume 2183)
    - Venus: Planet Sourcebook (Montreal, Canada: Dream Pod 9), 2002 (Volume 2180)
  - Justice, 80
    - Aaron Allston's Lands of Mystery (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1985 (Volume 2110)
    - Trail of the Gold Spike (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1984 (Volume 2115)
  - Kingdom Module, 81
    - Chybisa (Blaine, WA: Columbia Games ), 1987 (Volume 1199)
    - Kaldor (Blaine, WA: Columbia Games ), 1986 (Volume 1198)
    - Kanday (Blaine, WA: Columbia Games ), 1986 (Volume 1200)
    - Menglana (Blaine, WA: Columbia Games ), 1987 (Volume 1202)
    - Orbaal (Blaine, WA: Columbia Games ), 1987 (Volume 1201)
  - Lankhmar, 82
    - Avengers in Lankhmar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 627)
    - City of Adventure (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 626)
    - Cutthroats of Lankhmar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 628)
    - Lankhmar: City of Adventure (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 667)
    - Nehwon (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 663)
    - Prince of Lankhmar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 662)
    - Rogues in Lankhmar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 629)
    - Slayers of Lankhmar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 630)
    - Swords of Deceit (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 665)
    - Swords of the Undercity (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 666)
    - Tales of Lankhmar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 660)
    - Thieves of Lankhmar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 664)
    - Wonders of Lankhmar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 661)
  - Legend of the Five Rings, 83
    - Code of Bushido (no city: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1998 (Volume 505)
    - Game Master's Pack (no city: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1996 (Volume 507)
    - Honor's Veil (no city: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1996 (Volume 506)
    - Roleplaying in the Emerald Empire (no city: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1996 (Volume 503)
    - The Book of the Shadowlands: The Writings of Kuni Mokuna (no city: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1996 (Volume 502)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 1: The Way of the Dragon (Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1996 (Volume 496)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 3: The Way of the Crab (Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1998 (Volume 498)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 4: The Way of the Crane (Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1998 (Volume 499)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 6: The Way of the Lion (Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1998 (Volume 501)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 2: The Way of the Unicorn (Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1996 (Volume 497)
    - The Way of the Clans, Book 5: The Way of the Scorpion (Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1998 (Volume 500)
    - The Way of the Phoenix (Ontario, CA: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1998 (Volume 617)
    - Twilight Honor (no city: Alderac Entertainment Group), 1998 (Volume 504)
  - Marvel Super Heroes, 84
    - Avengers Assembled! (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1127)
    - Cat's-Paw (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1147)
    - Concrete Jungle: Official Character Roster (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 1129)
    - Fault Line (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 1144)
    - Judge's Screen: A Hero's Guide to New York (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1128)
    - Lone Wolves (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1148)
    - Murderworld! (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1149)
    - New York, New York (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 1130)
    - Project: Wideawake: Official Character Roster (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 1131)
    - Secret Wars (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1293)
    - Secret Wars II (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 1126)
    - The Breeder Bombs (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1151)
    - The Last Resort (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 1145)
    - Thunder Over Jotunheim (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 1146)
    - Time Trap (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1150)
    - Weapons Locker (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 1152)
  - MegaTraveller, 85
    - Gazelle Class: Close Escort (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1989 (Volume 1356)
    - Laboratory Ship (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1989 (Volume 1370)
    - MegaTraveller Players' Manual (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1987 (Volume 1169)
    - Subsidized Merchant (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1990 (Volume 1355)
  - Mekton, 86
    - Mecha Manual 2: Invasion Terra Files (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1995 (Volume 1392)
    - Mekton Empire (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1990 (Volume 1385)
    - Mekton Plus: Advanced Technical Manual (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1995 (Volume 1391)
    - Mekton Wars 1: Invasion Terra (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1995 (Volume 1383)
    - Mekton Zeta (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1995 (Volume 1386)
    - Mekton-Operation: Rimfire (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1993 (Volume 1384)
    - Mekton: Tactical Display (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1995 (Volume 1387)
    - Starblade Battalion (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1996 (Volume 1388)
  - Mercenaries, Spies and Private Eyes, 87
    - Mercenaries, Spies and Private Eyes (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1076)
    - Raid on Rajallapor (Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc. ), 1984 (Volume 1138)
  - Middle-Earth, 88
    - Angmar: Land of the Witch King (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1982 (Volume 1339)
    - Angus McBride's Characters of Middle-Earth (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 969)
    - Arnor (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1994 (Volume 1178)
    - Assassins of Dol Amroth (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1106)
    - Bree and the Barrow-Downs (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1984 (Volume 1098)
    - Brigands of Mirkwood (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1120)
    - Calenhad: A Beacon of Gondor (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 1324)
    - Creatures of Middle-Earth: A Bestiary of Animals and Monsters, 1st edition (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 965)
    - Dagorlad and the Dead Marshes (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1984 (Volume 1097)
    - Dark Mage of Rhudaur (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 1117)
    - Denizens of the Dark Wood (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 1100)
    - Dunland and the Southern Misty Mountains (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1327)
    - Empire of the Witch-King (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 1092)
    - Ents of Fangorn (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1328)
    - Erech and the Paths of the Dead (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1985 (Volume 1116)
    - Far Harad: The Scorched Land (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 1087)
    - Forest of Tears (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 1124)
    - Gates of Mordor (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1107)
    - Ghost Warriors (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 1123)
    - Ghosts of the Southern Anduin (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 1103)
    - Goblin-Gate and Eagle's Eyrie (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1985 (Volume 1115)
    - Gorgoroth (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 1094)
    - Greater Harad (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 1095)
    - Halls of the Elven-King (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 1330)
    - Haunted Ruins of the Dunlendings (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1985 (Volume 1091)
    - Havens of Gondor: Land of Belfalas (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1345)
    - Hazards of the Harad Wood (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 1101)
    - Hillmen of the Trollshaws (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1984 (Volume 1112)
    - Isengard and Northern Gondor (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1983 (Volume 1333)
    - Lords of Middle-Earth: Vol. I: The Immortals, 2nd edition (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 970)
    - Lords of Middle-Earth: Vol. II: The Mannish Races (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 966)
    - Lords of Middle-Earth: Vol. III: Hobbits, Dwarves, Ents, Orcs and Trolls, 1st edition (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 961)
    - Lorien and the Halls of the Elven Smiths (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1986 (Volume 1346)
    - Lost Realm of Cardolan (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1088)
    - Middle-Earth Role Playing (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1984 (Volume 1168)
    - Middle-Earth Role Playing Combat Screen and Reference Sheets (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 971)
    - Middle-Earth Role Playing, 2nd ed. (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1993 (Volume 1177)
    - Middle-Earth: A Campaign and Adventure Guidebook (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1982 (Volume 1341)
    - Middle-Earth: Adventure Guidebook II (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 1342)
    - Minas Ithil (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1991 (Volume 1340)
    - Minas Tirith (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 1343)
    - Mirkwood (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 1093)
    - Moria: The Dwarven City (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1984 (Volume 1332)
    - Mount Gundabad (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 1090)
    - Mouths of the Entwash (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 1119)
    - Nazgul's Citadel (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1991 (Volume 1329)
    - Northern Mirkwood: The Wood-Elves Realm (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1983 (Volume 1335)
    - Northwestern Middle-earth Gazetteer (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1992 (Volume 968)
    - Perils of the Sea of Rhun (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 1102)
    - Phantom of the Northern Marches (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1986 (Volume 1109)
    - Pirates of Pelargir (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 1108)
    - Raiders of Cardolan (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 1104)
    - Rangers of the North: The Kingdom of Arthedain (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1984 (Volume 1331)
    - Riders of Rohan (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1338)
    - Rivendell: The House of Elrond (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1114)
    - River Running (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1992 (Volume 1122)
    - Rogues of the Borderlands (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 1125)
    - Sea-Lords of Gondor (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1344)
    - Shadow in the South (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 1089)
    - Southern Mirkwood: Haunt of the Necromancer (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1983 (Volume 1334)
    - Teeth of Mordor (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 1325)
    - The Court of Ardor in Southern Middle-Earth (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1983 (Volume 1336)
    - The Grey Mountains (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1992 (Volume 1121)
    - The Necromancer's Lieutenant (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 1099)
    - The Tower of Cirith Ungol and Shelob's Lair (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1984 (Volume 1096)
    - Thieves of Tharbad (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1985 (Volume 1113)
    - Treasures of Middle-Earth: A Compendium of Magic Items (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 967)
    - Umbar: Haven of the Corsairs (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1982 (Volume 1337)
    - Warlords of the Desert (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 1118)
    - Weathertop: Tower of the Wind (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1326)
    - Woses of the Black Wood (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1987 (Volume 1105)
  - Monsters! Monsters!, 89
    - Monsters! Monsters!, 1st ed. (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1976 (Volume 1690)
  - Monstrous Arcana, 90
    - A Darkness Gathering (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 929)
    - Dawn of the Overmind (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 927)
    - Evil Tide (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 930)
    - Eye of Doom (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 804)
    - Eye of Pain (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 805)
    - Eye to Eye (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 803)
    - I, Tyrant (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 806)
    - Masters of the Eternal Night (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 928)
    - Night of the Shark (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 931)
    - Sea of Blood (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 932)
    - The Illithiad (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 933)
    - The Sea Devils (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 934)
  - Mystara, 91
    - Dungeon Master Survival Kit (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 834)
    - Joshuan's Almanac: Book of Facts (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 473)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 835)
    - Player's Survival Kit (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 833)
  - Odyssey, 92
    - Jakandor, Land of Legend (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 925)
    - Jakandor: Island of War (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 1452)
    - Jakandor: Isle of Destiny (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 1453)
  - Ogre, 93
    - Shockwave: An Ogre and G.E.V. Expansion Set (Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games), 1984 (Volume 1790)
  - Outer Planes, 94
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 821)
  - Pendragon, 95
    - Beyond the Wall: Pictland and the North (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 374)
    - Blood and Lust: Heroic Adventures in King Arthur's Britain (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 370)
    - King Arthur Pendragon: Epic Roleplaying in Legendary Britain (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 368)
    - King Arthur Pendragon: Epic Roleplaying in Legendary Britain, 4th edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1993 (Volume 362)
    - Knights Adventurous (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 365)
    - Land of the Giants: Scandinavia and the Beowulf Saga in the Time of King Arthur (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1996 (Volume 375)
    - Lordly Domains: The rights and responsibilities of landowners in the Age of King Arthur (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 376)
    - Pagan Shore: Ireland in the Age of King Arthur (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1994 (Volume 372)
    - Perilous Forest: Heroic Adventures in the forests and heaths of western Cumbria (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1992 (Volume 371)
    - Savage Mountains: Heroic Adventures in the Wilds of Cambria (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 369)
    - Saxons! Wolves in the Fold of Arthur's Britain (Mountain View, CA: Green Knight Publishing), 1999 (Volume 360)
    - Tales of Chivalry and Romance: Adventures in the World of King Arthur Pendragon (Mountain View, CA: Green Knight Publishing), 1999 (Volume 361)
    - The Boy King: Arthur Claims the Throne of Britain (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 366)
    - The Boy King: Arthur Claims the Throne of Britian, 2nd edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 367)
    - The Grey Knight (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), undated (Volume 363)
    - The Spectre King: Heroic Adventures in Legendary Britain (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1992 (Volume 373)
    - Tournament of Dreams (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1987 (Volume 364)
  - Penumbra, 96
    - Three Days to Kill (no city: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 476)
  - Planescape, 97
    - A Guide to the Astral Plane (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 405)
    - A Guide to the Ethereal Plane (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 1008)
    - Dead Gods (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 1009)
    - Doors to the Unknown (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 404)
    - Faces of Evil: The Fiends (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1997 (Volume 403)
    - Faction War (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 1012)
    - Fires of Dis (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 455)
    - Harbinger House (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 412)
    - In the Abyss (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 413)
    - In the Cage: A Guide to Sigil (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 409)
    - Monstrous Compendium, Appendix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 416)
    - Monstrous Compendium, Appendix II (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 415)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix III (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 401)
    - On Hallowed Ground (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 406)
    - Something Wild (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 411)
    - Tales from the Infinite Staircase (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 402)
    - The Deva Spark (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 454)
    - The Eternal Boundary (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 414)
    - The Factol's Manifesto (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 453)
    - The Great Modron March (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 1010)
    - The Inner Planes (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 1011)
    - The Planewalker's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 407)
    - Uncaged: Faces of Sigil (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 410)
    - Well of Worlds (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 417)
  - Prime Directive, 98
    - Graduation Exercise (Amarillo, TX: Task Force Games), 1994 (Volume 475)
    - Prime Adventures 1 (Amarillo, TX: Task Force Games), 1995 (Volume 474)
    - The Federation (Amarillo, TX: Task Force Games), 1994 (Volume 456)
    - Uprising (Amarillo, TX: Task Force Games), 1994 (Volume 457)
  - Prince Valiant, 99
    - Prince Valiant: The Story Telling Game (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1989 (Volume 383)
  - Pulp Dungeons, 100
    - An Infestation of Kobalds (Lake Geneva, WI: Destination Games.), 1996 (Volume 1792)
  - Quicksilver Fantasies, 101
    - Carnival in Windemere (Post Falls, Id: Quicksilver Fantasies), 1981 (Volume M4)
    - Jouney from Pigour (Post Falls, Id: Quicksilver Fantasies), 1982 (Volume M4)
  - Ravenloft, 102
    - A Guide to Transylvania: a Masque of the Red Death Accessory (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 914)
    - Adam's Wrath (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 753)
    - Book of Crypts (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 759)
    - Carnival (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 1023)
    - Champions of the Mists (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 1018)
    - Children of the Night: Ghost (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 1021)
    - Children of the Night: the Created (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1999 (Volume 1016)
    - Children of the Night: Vampires (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 915)
    - Children of the Night: Werebeasts (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1998 (Volume 1015)
    - Chilling Tales (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 746)
    - Circle of Darkness (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 747)
    - Dark of the Moon (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 754)
    - Death Ascendant (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 913)
    - Death Unchained (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 912)
    - Domains of Dread (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1997 (Volume 1013)
    - Feast of Goblyns (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 767)
    - Forged of Darkness (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 910)